door board meeting for Monday, March 20th, 2023, the invocation by Mr. Steve Whitehill,
see you here, our deputy fire chief. Would you like to do it, words please?
Heavenly Father, we're thankful for this day, we're thankful we're able to come and be a part of
the business of the community and just be with our council members as they make decisions that affect
the solence in your name we pray in it. I'd like to introduce you to the light on its states,
for public input or on scheduled personal appearances, five consent agenda.
Oh, sorry, we usually do it in the next one. So we do have one of the on scheduled,
are the public input, single, canongus, canongus. Sorry, you go ahead and go to the podium.
I don't know if I'm back, it's going to, you'll get three minutes and the council won't respond.
If there's a response needed, then we'll get it to you either riding through the end or somehow to you.
Okay, Mr. Nookanga, last year in July after my partners unexpected passing due to medical issues
that were not God sent, I was homeless for two months. I had a HUD voucher, but could not find one
bedroom anywhere. I'm on SSI and can only afford so much for rent utilities. I ended up teaming up with a
friend I thought I could trust. We had found a two bedroom that was had approved. I put my friend on my
HUD and on my lease thinking I could trust her. Not knowing that she owed the utility company here in town
1,200, 73 dollars and 86 cents on past utility debt. Before even signing the lease or teaming up to find a home
with her, I had to ask her with Grand Lake Mental Health if there was anything I needed to know. She said no,
but was working on trying to get a disability and a job that she never got. She basically lied to me.
The utility company would not turn on the utilities at our new home without in my name because she was on my lease.
I was homeless, had nowhere to go and had already paid a deposit in first month's rent for the two bedroom. I was trapped.
I ended up absorbing her debt and signing a payment plan, contract of $40 a month as a part of my utility bill.
11 months into living with me, she moved out and left to another state.
staff room for the purpose of executive session at the completion of a job at gender item
22 of the regular meeting in the United States Council.